[Music] php a dynamic interpreted scripting
[音乐]php 一种动态解释脚本
language for building interactive websites on the server despite the
语言，用于在服务器上构建交互式网站，尽管
haters pronouncing it dead it remains one of the most popular languages for
仇恨者认为它已死，但它仍然是后端 Web 开发最流行的语言之一，
back-end web development it powers content management systems like
它为内容管理系统（如
wordpress top-tier websites like wikipedia and countless others via
wordpress 等顶级网站，如维基百科和 无数其他人通过
frameworks like laravel and symphony hell man even facebook uses it although
laravel 和 symphonyhell man 等框架使用它，尽管
they built a custom compiler to convert it to machine code on their servers it
他们构建了一个自定义编译器来将其转换为服务器上的机器代码，它
was created in 1994 by rasmus lyrdorf to manage his personal home page clever
是 rasmus lyrdorf 于 1994 年创建的，用于管理他的个人主页聪明的
acronym but it sounds lame for a language that powers multi-billion
首字母缩略词，但听起来很蹩脚 一种为数十亿
dollar enterprises so today we practice cognitive dissonance to tell ourselves
美元企业提供动力的语言，所以今天我们练习认知失调来告诉自己
php stands for hypertext preprocessor it has a special place in history because
php 代表超文本预处理器，它在历史上占有特殊地位，因为
it predates javascript and was one of the first languages to be embedded
它早于 javascript，并且是最早
directly in html allowing websites to be built dynamically on a server it's open
直接嵌入 html 的语言之一，允许网站在服务器上动态构建它是
source and was one of the technologies that revolutionized the web by making
开源的并且是技术之一 IES通过使普通人可以访问应用程序开发而彻底改变了网络
application development accessible to the average person its interpreter is
它的解释器是
implemented in c and has a syntax inspired by perl to get started create a
用c实现的，并且具有受perl启发的语法来开始创建一个
php file and add some basic html to it within this file you can go into php
php文件并在这个文件中添加一些基本的html你可以进入php
mode by opening a question mark php tag the code within these tags will be
模式 通过打开一个问号 php 标签，这些标签中的代码将
rendered on the server use echo to output a value and the location of the
在服务器上呈现使用 echo输出一个值和标签的位置
tag to declare a variable give it a name that starts with a dollar sign followed
来声明一个变量，给它一个以美元符号开头的名称，
by a value it's a weekly typed language so no type annotations are necessary it
后跟一个值 每周键入的语言，因此不需要类型注释
also comes with a large number of predefined variables geared towards web
它还带有大量面向 Web 开发的预定义变量，
development like git post and cookie which contain information about the
例如 git post 和 cookie，其中包含有关
incoming http request now when this code is rendered on your server it will
传入 http 请求的信息，现在当此代码在您的服务器上呈现时，它将
output an html string with the php tags being replaced by whatever you echoed
输出一个 html 带有php标签的字符串被您回显的任何内容替换
the language also supports multiple programming paradigms you have first
该语言还支持多种编程范例，您拥有
class functions which can be assigned to variables or used anonymously as
一流的功能 可以分配给变量或匿名用作
arguments and it has tons and tons of built-in functions to do pretty much
参数，它有大量的内置函数可以做几乎
anything a web developer could ever imagine doing it also has a complete
任何 Web 开发人员可以想象的事情。它还有一个完整的
object model where you can define classes with inheritance to implement
对象模型，您可以在其中定义具有继承的类来实现
object-oriented patterns we're currently on php version 8 which has all the
对象 面向模式，我们目前使用的是 php 版本 8，它具有
features you would expect from a modern pragmatic language every web developer
每个 Web 开发人员
should be familiar with it because statistically there's a 78.5 chance that
都应该熟悉的现代实用语言所期望的所有功能，因为从统计数据来看，您客
your client's website is running the personal homepage language this has been
户的网站运行个人主页语言的可能性为 78.5
php in 100 seconds hit the like button if you want to see more short videos
100 秒内 php如果您想看更多这样的短视频，请点击“赞”按钮，
like this thanks for watching and i will see you in the next one
谢谢收看，我会在下一个